Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
ALL: (CHANTING)
Retchid Kat! Retchid Kat!
They love you. Kill 'em.
(CROWD CHEERING)
SAMMY: Yeah.
Yeah. the Kat.
Yeah.
(SAMMY WHOOPING)
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(STRING QUARTET PLAYING)
No. no. no. no.
Mr. Brimley. it is
a violin. not a saw.
We only have till
Saturday to get this right.
We can stay here
all night if we have to.
Carter. dude. get it right.
LAWSON: Again from the 14th.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(CLATTERING)
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
(RAT SQUEAKING)
(RATS SQUEALING)
(SCREAMING)
MAN: The terror
Ooh. smoothies.
I need some ice.
It's in the freezer.
I'm just warming up first.
It's going to be
cold over there.
You should've
started this earlier.
I think we have a problem.
All right. We can go upstairs.
With the ice. There isn't any.
Oh. no.
It's warm. Everything's
going to spoil.
How much of this do you
think we can fit in the blender?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah. Burkhardt.
Where?
Detectives
Burkhardt and Griffin.
this is Assistant
Principal Grace Kaplan.
She found the body
about an hour ago.
Says it's Paul Lawson.
a music teacher here.
He was the director
of the music program.
I just can't believe this has
happened. It's so horrible.
Well. do you want to
tell us what happened?
I saw the car when I
came in this morning.
It's a little unusual for
anyone to be here before me.
that's why I walked
over to the car.
I'm sorry. It's okay.
Looks to me like it
happened sometime last night.
He's been dead for a few hours.
Car's locked. We
kept it that way.
Got some evidence inside.
didn't want it to get away.
Death by rat?
WU: Looks like.
Oh. God. rats. I
can't stand rats.
NICK: Coroner here?
Yeah. waiting for you.
So is Animal Control.
Nobody wants to open the
door until you guys give the okay.
Fingerprints done?
Yeah. we're good to go.
Open it up.
Let's go.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Ooh.
We also found some cages in
the bushes you should look at.
Whoever chucked these didn't
make much of an effort to hide them.
Geiger Pest Control.
We know them?
They're in northeast
Portland. by the river.
According to the
Assistant Principal.
Lawson was here late last night
rehearsing for a school performance
supposed to happen on Saturday.
Glad I'm not a ticket holder.
Anyone see him
leave? Still checking.
But we got names of the four
students he was rehearsing.
HANK: Nice house.
Nice cars.
And bad things still happen.
NICK: What time
did practice end?
A little after 10:00.
HANK: Did Lawson leave with you?
No. He always stays to close up.
Did anybody see him
leave the building?
HANK: Did any of you see
anything strange when you left?
Anything unusual?
Maybe a car you
hadn't seen before?
Somebody standing around?
We just went to
our cars and left.
It was late. so we
had to get home.
We still had homework.
Did Dr. Lawson seem a
little nervous last night?
Maybe a little upset?
SARAH: Yes. but that was. um...
That was just Dr. Lawson.
We found some cages in
the brush near the parking lot.
Did you see anybody near
there when you left for your cars?
What kind of cages?
Used for trapping rodents.
No.
Well. if you can think
of anything else...
Roddy Geiger went to our school.
Who?
His dad's an exterminator.
Geiger Pest Control?
Roddy wouldn't do this.
Geiger's son goes
to your school.
He did.
He was suspended
a couple days ago.
Why?
If this is about that situation.
maybe you'd better
speak to the school.
That's a very troubled boy.
I don't think it's appropriate
to talk to the kids about him.
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
Nice house.
Yeah. Nice cars.
Nice music.
It's coming from over there.
Captivated audience.
Roddy Geiger?
Yeah?
I'm Detective Burkhardt.
this is Detective Griffin.
You're pretty
good on that violin.
What do you want? We want
to ask you a few questions.
You cops?
Well. we've been called worse.
What do you want here?
Are you Mr. Geiger?
You're here about that
teacher dying. aren't you?
I heard all about it.
Well. we had
nothing to do with it.
Take it easy. sir. We just
want to ask a few questions.
Who died?
Dr. Lawson was found
dead in his car this morning.
What?
You don't talk to them until I
find out what they're going to do.
What are you going
to do. arrest us?
You going to arrest me?
You're going to arrest my boy?
Sir. you need to calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down.
I know what's going on here.
They're trying to blame us
for what happened up there.
and I'm tired of them
treating us like garbage.
Stop. Don't move. Take
your hands off of him.
Leave him alone.
Leave him alone!
Stop resisting! You're
only making it worse.
I got him.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I don't want to hurt
you. Yeah. you do.
You're a Grimm.
You want to kill me.
I'm not going to kill you.
But you keep this up...
You're going to get hurt.
Assaulting an officer. resisting
arrest hasn't made this any better.
Now you might think
about a little cooperation.
Where were you last night?
Up in the mountains.
A lot of mountains around here.
Off Highway 26. past Sandy.
What were you doing?
I catch rats for a living.
I don't kill 'em
if I don't have to.
I turn the healthy ones loose.
Can anyone testify to that? No.
Where was your son last night?
Home. Anybody home with him?
No.
You can kind of see the problem
we're faced with here. can't you?
We had nothing to do
with that teacher dying.
Your son was
suspended for fighting.
Didn't that make you mad?
If it were me. I
think I'd be mad.
Don't try to understand me.
How do you explain the
cages being up at the school?
They were stolen two nights ago.
HANK: You report it?
Yeah. sure. How many cops do
you think they put on stolen rat cages?
Those kids at that school
know what I do for a living.
and they never
let Roddy forget it.
You know. my boy's a prodigy.
Better than anyone
at that school.
Better than anyone in this city.
But that didn't matter
because of what I do.
What kind of relationship did
Roddy have with the teacher?
Roddy didn't need him.
And he let Dr. Lawson know it?
He couldn't hide the obvious.
Maybe Roddy snapped last night.
What was the fight
at school about?
They don't like me.
I don't like them.
Yeah. well. you
don't hide it very well.
Don't I? Really? That's so sad.
Look. I get it.
You're the outsider. No one
understands the world the way you do.
Maybe you shouldn't
expect them to.
I certainly don't
expect a Grimm to.
Do you know many Grimms?
I don't need to.
Okay. so you know all about me
because you've heard a
bunch of stories about me.
and you know everything
you need to know.
So if I asked these
kids at school.
they'd tell me everything
I need to know.
and it'd all be true. right?
Just because they don't know me.
that doesn't mean that you do.
According to school records.
Dr. Lawson reported you for attacking
Carter Brimley and Trey Harrison.
Yeah. I attacked them
after they jumped me.
According to Marvin... Marvin?
Their little butter-boy?
'Cause he wouldn't lie.
Maybe this thing didn't turn
out the way you planned.
Maybe you were just
trying to scare your teacher.
I wasn't there last night.
Where were you?
I was at a rave.
Where?
Down by the river.
Be more specific.
It's an old building
on Front Street.
Anybody there with you?
Only about a couple hundred.
Could any of them identify you?
One.
Got a name?
So you can arrest him for
putting on an illegal rave?
Yeah. That's my dream.
Look. you either prove to
me where you were last night.
or you go to jail.
WU: You're never
going to believe this.
I talked to Sammy. the
guy who put on the rave.
Your perp is DJ Retchid Kat.
Who's DJ Retchid Kat?
Tell me you know.
Of course I know.
Everybody knows.
Who's DJ Retchid Kat?
Only the most famous
raver in Portland.
Not that men of your age would
know what I'm talking about.
You didn't know either.
Not until I talked to Sammy.
DJ Retchid Kat always
wears a big cat head.
and Sammy is the only
one who knows who he is.
and he swears it is your guy.
So his alibi's good.
But not his dad's.
Except why would he leave
his cages at the school?
Not so clever. Unless he wanted
us to believe somebody stole them.
Then it's clever.
Let Roddy go. hold onto the dad?
Absolutely.
Not to mention. he
assaulted an officer.
He deserves a little
downtime for that alone.
You're free to go.
What about my dad?
Not until we verify his alibi.
You know he can't do that.
Pretty excited
about being let go.
Oh. yeah. I had to
stop him from yodeling.
Harper called. Dead
guy wants to see us.
He died of a heart attack.
So the rats scared him to death?
Well. they didn't help.
But he was on digoxin and
angiotensin for his heart.
He was kind of high
up on death's to-do list.
So the rats were put
in the car to kill him.
If they knew
about his condition.
But no guarantee a scare like
that would trigger a heart attack.
Prank gone bad.
Yeah. or a threat.
Then it's probably Roddy's dad.
A homicide occurred
in the course
of an intentional maiming of the
victim. so it's aggravated murder.
I did find something
interesting in my other autopsy.
What other autopsy?
Oh. man.
There goes lunch.
Well. speaking of...
A rat's stomach is like a road
map to where they've been.
Here we have some
undigested bits of your victim.
and some colored
cloth and nylon fibers
that didn't match any of
the clothes he was wearing.
They were chewing on
something else in the car?
Probably before
Dr. Lawson got in.
Take a look at this.
Oh. do I have to?
It's green and red.
Same colors as the music school.
Let's find out if it matches
anything in Lawson's car.
"Rats dine on beloved teacher."
That's a little cold. Guess
who came to dinner?
What do you got on this?
Press wants a statement.
We have one suspect in
custody. Has he been charged?
We have enough evidence.
but we're not sure he's our guy.
We're waiting on
some lab results.
Well. I got a dead popular teacher
at an expensive private school.
I'd like an answer before
politics screw things up.
What are you doing here?
The cops just arrested my dad.
What?
Whoever did this wanted
them to think it was him.
Or me.
That's what everybody thinks.
You think it was me?
You were the one
that got suspended.
That was bogus. I
thought you knew that.
Why didn't you say anything?
They're my friends.
And I'm what?
Someone I used to care about.
Used to?
Roddy...
So now you're with Carter?
I can't do this.
You still love me.
I can't keep sneaking
out to be with you.
And if you didn't put the
rats in his car. then who did?
Your boyfriend.
He would not do that.
Yeah. he would.
To get to you.
and get rid of me.
What are you doing here?
I thought that this was
over and done with.
Your father will go ballistic.
Please go get in the house.
Stay away from my daughter.
Stay away from my family.
What are you
doing here. rat-boy?
Ah. ah. ah. ah. ah.
Come on. Do it.
I wonder what the police
will say when they get here.
You're going to pay.
Some of us can afford to.
(THUDS)
The investigation is ongoing.
Because of the unusual
nature of the death.
we are taking extra measures to make
sure that nothing has been overlooked.
Dr. Lawson was an important
member of our community.
and. uh. an inspiration
to a lot of young people.
His untimely death has
caused a great deal of distress.
and I promise that
every effort will be made
to bring the person or
persons responsible to justice.
I'll take your questions now.
Preliminary lab
reports just came in
on the fibers found
in the rat's stomach.
Some of them were nylon.
the kind found in car carpeting.
BMW. Audi. Porsche.
You know. the kind of
vehicles we don't drive.
And neither do the Geigers.
The colored fibers
are from blankets.
There's a Mrs. Jessup
here demanding to see you.
She's got. uh...
How can I say this?
Smoke coming out
of a lot of orifices.
Good luck.
Why hasn't Roddy
Geiger been arrested?
He came to my house and
he harassed my daughter.
This boy is out of control.
He got himself thrown
out of school for fighting...
We can't arrest Roddy Geiger
or anybody without evidence.
Well. then get some
before somebody else dies.
I do not want him
coming to my house.
Why is he coming to your house?
My daughter went out
with him a couple of times.
Now he thinks he owns her.
If my husband sees him
again. I'm afraid of what he'll do.
That boy does not
belong in our school.
Or in your neighborhood?
Shouldn't you be
writing this down?
I am filing a report. aren't I?
I haven't had that much fun
since that drunk threw up
on me at the Christmas party.
Wasn't that Sergeant Wu?
It was. and I'm meeting
him at Clark Lewis for a drink.
Want to go?
Don't answer.
You've got Juliette.
you're in love. you got a life.
Go live it. my child.
Leave alcohol to those of
us who are still searching.
Reinigen?
They're bottom of
the food chain. man.
Let me tell ya. the
food in their chain?
Gourmet is not their forte.
But they're rarely violent unless
they're pushed to the limit. right?
Correct.
If you know all that.
what are you doing here?
How would you feel
about talking to a...
Reinigen?
I'm not protecting
anyone for you. am I?
Last time I protected
someone for you
was not exactly a
pleasant experience.
How is that guy. by the way?
Were they able to
sew his arm back on?
Uh. I don't think he's going to be
beating anybody up with it again.
Look. you like music.
right? I mean. you play.
I don't do parties.
This kid. he is
pretty incredible.
At what? Violin.
He got a scholarship to
the Von Hamelin Institute.
Is this about that teacher
who wound up as ratatouille?
Okay. some people think
he was involved. I don't.
This kid is a stick of dynamite.
He knows I'm a Grimm. And a cop.
So he's not exactly
open to... Yeah. yeah.
A heart to heart.
I got the picture.
You think he'll listen to
me 'cause I play the cello?
Just so you know.
Reinigen and Blutbaden
are not drinking buddies.
I've never been much
of a do-gooder. Nick.
The only bleeding
heart I ever had was a...
I mean. that's in the
past. I'm just saying.
Look. I was
different growing up.
and I have a feeling
you were. too.
Monroe. this kid just
needs a little bit of help.
He's not a rapper. is he?
I mean. nothing against
rappers. it's just. you know...
Where's the melody?
BUD: (GROANS) Damn it!
(GROANS) I can't get
this damn screw loose.
How long has this been going on?
Oh. since 4:30. I'm sorry.
I'm going as fast as I can.
Will you be done tonight?
What. do you think
I'm going to sleep here?
Aw. crap! I cut my hand.
Ooh. I'll get a bandage.
I hate this model.
It's a deathtrap.
Look. it's trying to kill me.
(NERVOUSLY) Please.
please. don't. don't hurt me.
Oh. God. Oh. please!
What happened? What did you do?
Nothing. He just ran out?
It looked like he
was terrified of you.
Yeah. I know.
Well. that's really
weird. isn't it. Nick?
Maybe it was the refrigerator.
You know. he said it
was trying to kill him.
Well. now what do we do?
Go out.
I'm telling you. he's got
an instinct for people.
Most of the time. he's right.
Well. it's too bad Nick
wasn't your partner
when you met your last wife.
That's cold. You got to
learn to say no to temptation.
Hey. how 'bout some dinner?
I'm tempted. but no.
I've got a big day tomorrow.
I've got to get some sleep.
So you're paying. right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
(CHUCKLES) Hey. Bill. Yeah?
Lonely Sergeant
needs a steak over here.
Yeah. next week
will be fine. Okay.
Hey. Miss Schade. right?
Detective... Griffin.
Hank. That's right.
Sorry. I should've
remembered that.
You saved my life.
So how have you been?
Busy. How've you been?
Busy. Which is good right now.
Well. you take care. You. too.
Hey. Hank?
I don't suppose you'd
want to save me again.
From what?
My business meeting canceled.
and I've got this great
table. an empty chair.
Maybe it's time
for a little payback.
Can I buy you dinner?
Yeah. sure. Sounds great.
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
You were kicking some butt
on that Brahms concerto. man.
It was brilliantly executed.
Very fluid.
Who are you?
Monroe. We don't
know each other.
I'm a friend of
Detective Burkhardt's.
No. thanks. Uh-uh.
I wasn't finished.
Now. I don't normally
do this kind of thing.
but we both know who Nick is.
And he is not like the other
ones we've heard about.
Capisce?
Believe it or not. he's
worried about you.
And he knew you
wouldn't talk to him.
so he thought maybe
you would talk to me.
About what? About
not being stupid.
He said you had
talent. man. and it's true.
I just heard it.
And I've been
around a lot of people
who thought they had talent.
Yours truly is one of them.
But the real thing. man.
The real thing is
an impossibility.
You don't know where it
comes from. or what made it.
but it's one of the mysteries
of life that lifts us all
out of the misery of average.
And one of the problems
is you people who have it
don't think it's any big deal.
That just pisses me off.
So the bottom line is
you don't throw that away.
Is this going well?
I mean. I feel like it should be
a little more back and forth. no?
I don't know.
Yeah. you do.
Just 'cause you're young. doesn't
mean you're smarter than me.
Okay? So...
Basically what we're saying
here is. uh. just don't blow it.
Man. I'm tired.
I'm not used to this intimate
one-on-one thing. you know?
I know you're probably
kind of weirded out.
a Reinigen getting
advice from a Blutbad.
It doesn't ever really
happen. but listen to me.
Sometimes our lives collide
in the most bizarre ways.
Right?
Still nothing? Okay.
Well. you know
what I'm saying. right?
Take care. And if you
ever need anything...
Call me.
All right.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Hello? This is Officer
Clay from Central Jail.
Is this Roddy Geiger? Yeah.
I have to inform you.
your father was injured
when he refused
to enter his cell.
Is he okay?
He's being treated
in the infirmary.
He's got a concussion.
No visitors for 48 hours.
Maybe you arrested him once.
Who? The refrigerator repairman.
Maybe that's why
he was so upset.
Right. Yeah.
I didn't even think of that.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Burkhardt.
Hey. so I talked to
Roddy. The Reinigen kid?
And I don't want to
toot my own horn here.
but I think I made some inroads.
Gave him a lot to think about.
Well. thanks. I appreciate it.
No problem at all.
I think that kid's going to be
on a little different tack now.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(RODDY YELLING)
Once we got confirmation
that the nylon fibers
in the rat's stomach
were used in German cars.
we ruled out the teacher's car.
We ran every
student registration
at the Von Hamelin Institute to see if
we could find a match with the fibers.
I'm guessing half the student
body drive German cars.
Actually we narrowed it
down to just BMWs and Audis
that use the nylon
we're looking for.
But the style is
only used in SUVs.
We clicked it down from
there to a half-dozen students.
One of them had a fight
with Roddy. Carter Brimley.
And he drives a BMW X5.
which is a match with the fibers.
Get a warrant.
Yeah.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRASHES)
Just talked to Sarah.
Roddy came over to
her house yesterday.
He knows we did it.
Saying it and proving it
are two different things.
She asked me if we did it.
You weren't dumb
enough to say yes.
No. but I'm a little
bit freaking out here.
Everybody knows Roddy is
a lot better player than Carter.
and the only reason
he got the chair
is because we got him booted.
and so he could be next to Sarah.
Grow some.
Check it. DJ Retchid
Kat rave tonight.
Awesome.
(PHONE BEEPING) Oh.
Are we going? Well. the men are.
This is ridiculous.
My son had nothing to do with
what happened to Dr. Lawson.
That's what we're
here to find out.
Then I should call a lawyer.
Well. that's your
privilege. sir.
but you'll still need
to open your son's car.
Or we'll have to do it by force.
This is great. This is
where my tax money goes.
What do you think
you're going to find?
There's nothing in there.
That's what they all say.
We got holes. Bag it.
Holes? What does that mean?
What do we have here?
Not a chocolate chip.
And the color of the carpeting
matches the fibers we've got.
Sir. we're going to
impound your car.
What? Tell us where your son is.
I'm not saying anything
to you till I talk to a lawyer.
Well. in that case. we'll have to
put a warrant out for his arrest.
he'll be taken to Central
Jail... (CELL PHONE RINGING)
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
he's just out with friends.
Uh-huh. Who?
He left with Trey
about an hour ago.
They were going to see a movie.
Nick. we got a fire
at the Geiger house.
You got this? Yeah. got it. Go.
Somebody let the dogs out.
And I'm guessing it's
the same somebody
who trashed Roddy's room.
We'd better get
to Sarah's house.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
We need to talk
to your daughter.
Why? She hasn't done anything.
We need to know where
she is. She might be in danger.
She's with friends
at the movies.
You need to call her.
(PHONE DIALING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
She didn't take her phone.
I think we got it.
MAN: The terror
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
Are we in the wrong place?
We're the only ones here.
Maybe we're not
supposed to park here.
Who cares where we park?
It's started. I can hear it.
What are you doing?
Did you guys have
anything to do with it?
What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
Are you crazy?
Come on. let's go.
Did you get Roddy suspended?
No. he jumped us. and
we just defended ourselves.
What's the matter? You
want to be with rat-boy now?
Shut up.
Are you coming or
not? 'Cause we're going.
(FAINT TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
Where is it?
It's coming from underground.
Oh. man. that is so literal.
Oh. this is so sick.
I... I don't know if
we should do this.
Ah. what's your problem?
Come on. it's already started.
My old man called three times.
Yeah. mine did. too.
(CHUCKLES) My
mom called four times.
Dude. don't they
know we're at a movie?
Yeah. that's Trey's
car. Plates match.
Music's coming
from the building.
(TECHNO MUSIC GETTING LOUDER)
SARAH: Okay.
this is really weird.
This way. Through here.
(WHOOPING) Oh. man.
This is tight! This is so cool.
MARVIN: Check this place. y'all.
(WHOOPING) Yeah!
Yes! Yeah.
SARAH: Sweet.
We're the only ones here.
Historical.
SARAH: Oh. wow.
(MUSIC STOPS PLAYING)
What the hell. man. We early?
(DISTORTED VOICE) You lied.
(ECHOES)
What?
You stole the cages.
You ratted the car.
You killed him.
Whoa.
How does he know that?
You did it.
He told me. and I
didn't believe him.
Now it's your turn. SARAH: What?
Oh. my God. It's Roddy.
DJ Retchid Kat is Roddy.
This isn't funny. man.
Oh. my God. Oh. my God.
Rats!
RODDY: You framed my dad.
MARVIN: They're everywhere!
(ALL SCREAMING)
HANK: Oh. God. This is not good.
(SARAH SCREAMS)
How does it feel?
(SHRIEKS) Oh. my
God! Oh. my God!
Dude. let's go! Go! Go!
Run! SARAH: Please
get them off me!
Get them off! Get them off!
RODDY: Sarah!
Get off! Get off!
(GUN FIRING)
NICK: Oh. my God.
Hang on!
(WHIMPERING)
TREY: We didn't mean
it. It was an accident.
We never meant
to hurt Dr. Lawson.
We just wanted to scare him.
And make it look
like Roddy did it
so Carter could take his place.
Roddy was better than all of us.
Will you tell him
that I'm sorry?
Maybe you should do that.
Guess they're going to
have to face the music.
Really? You went there?
Somebody had to.
You want my weapon?
Sarah had nothing to do with it.
And she didn't
know her friends did.
Was this worth it?
They deserved it.
Yeah. that's not what I asked.
They never would've
admitted anything.
Can't say I ever used
rats to get a confession.
You're lucky no one got hurt.
Except Dr. Lawson.
Mmm!
How many rats? What?
For the report. How many rats
do you think were down there?
I'm sorry. I didn't
stop to count.
I'd like to put a million. 'cause
that's what it seemed like.
Put a thousand. No one's
going to believe a million.
Nobody's going to
believe a thousand.
What are we going
to charge this kid with?
Well. if it was up
to me... Nothing.
We got to charge
him with something.
He took a bunch of
kids and tried to hurt 'em.
With music and rats and violins?
No one forced those
kids to go down there.
So all we got on Roddy is an
illegal rave with five people?
D.A.'s not going to want this. plus
they got to deal with all those other kids.
How's a kid do
something like that?
Well. he was an outsider.
He got pushed too far.
No. no. I got that. I'm talking
about how he got all those rats
to go down to that building.
Oh. I don't know.
There are a lot
of rats in the city.
Maybe they like raves.
Hmm. It was a rat rave.
Do not put that in the report.
(CHUCKLES)
Want a slice? Sure.
Oh! (LAUGHS)
Damn! That's not funny!
My man. Oh. it's funny
if you knew it was there.
Chuckle now. but payback's
a bitch and she bites.
(SQUEAKS)
This will remind me.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Uh. I waited until he left.
I just want to get my tools.
and I'll be out of your hair.
(NERVOUSLY) I don't want
any trouble. I'm a peaceful man.
It's all right. He doesn't
even remember you.
Uh. what do you mean? From
whatever time he arrested you.
Arrested? What are
you talking about?
Isn't that what
you're talking about?
Look. you're never going to
see me again. I swear to God.
What about the refrigerator?
They're sending
another guy over.
Why can't you just fix it?
Look. lady.
I don't know what kind of
games you two are playing here.
I got three kids at
home. I don't need this.
I never did anything bad.
He's got no reason
to come after me.
Please make sure he knows that.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org